<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/QuestionResponse.xsd">
    <Question id="20070911155951AALY4K4" type="Answered">
        <Subject>Amsterdam?</Subject>
        <Content>My boyfriend and I are planning a trip with another couple to Amsterdam.  Have you been there? Is there a better time of the year to go? Preferred way of travel? Any and all info would be great!
</Content>
        <Date>2007-09-11 15:59:51</Date>
        <Timestamp>1189551591</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20070911155951AALY4K4</Link>
        <Category id="396545531">Netherlands</Category>
        <UserId>0xtQqa9taa</UserId>
        <UserNick>crazydaisy</UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>7</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>1</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>Best time of year for Amsterdam (or The Netherlands) in my opinion is end of may, early june.
Not too many tourists yet, acceptable weather.

Travel - in the large cities (Amsterdam, Rotterdam, Haarlem, Den Haag, Utrecht) busses and trams are very convenient to get around. Between cities you can use the train system.
You can also rent a car if you feel comfortable - a good and cheap company is www.sixty.com. (used them myself. very satisfied).

To give more info, you might want to give some details as to what your preferences are. Do you like museums, nature, beach, festivals? Do you like to take other trips besides to Amsterdam?

Feel free to contact me through my profile for more info.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>e5f4c192231c92a0d059825b151f7553aa</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>U_S_S_Enterprise</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1189589290</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1190310155</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20070616052334AAWnEhI" type="Answered">
        <Subject>amsterdam?</Subject>
        <Content>we have this project in our world history class.....actually, it&#039;s a long story but anyway i need info about amsterdam. is it true that prostitution is legal there? do  people there smoke weed? and all the other stuff i need to know about amsterdam.
</Content>
        <Date>2007-06-16 05:23:34</Date>
        <Timestamp>1181996614</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20070616052334AAWnEhI</Link>
        <Category id="396545531">Netherlands</Category>
        <UserId>AA11625784</UserId>
        <UserNick>smashmouth</UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/sc/28172/answers1/images/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>6</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>0</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>There are several common misconceptions on Amsterdam:
The rules that apply to Amsterdam apply to the entire country of Netherlands.  Netherlands is a very liberal country, but the truth is most of the local people and countries citizens do not smoke weed or use prostitutes (even though they are widely available).  As you probably know, doing things aren&#039;t as enticing when you are actually allowed to do them.

First about drugs:
Marijuana is technically not legal in Netherlands.  However it is &quot;tolerated&quot;.  This means that there are certain places that you can buy weed without having to worry about getting in trouble (the police turn the other way so to speak).  You can buy them in &quot;coffee shops&quot; along with several other drugs that would be considered illegal in many parts of the world.  However it is still illegal to smoke on the street (although sometimes you can get away with this too).

Prostitution is legal, and a highly regulated industry.  If you go to the Red light district in Amsterdam you can see windows with women in them for hire.  The most expensive are the closest and it goes less and less expensive the farther you get out. 

Amsterdam is a haven for tourists who want to indulge, but from what I have seen people that live there often don&#039;t take part in this as much as tourists.

The Netherlands is a wonderful country that has a lot to offer and see (besides for the drugs and prostitutes :) ).  When you have the chance you should travel there.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>AA12008040</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>NotoFroto</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1182008600</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1182516166</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20120220173034AAj5foC" type="Answered">
        <Subject>AMSTERDAM?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?</Subject>
        <Content>I&#039;m planning to travel to Amsterdam in the next few weeks with my 2 friends for 3 dayz...I&#039;ve heard Amsterdam has alot more to do than the legal weed and porn cinemas...I heard it has beautiful places like museums.Etc.

Can someone please give me advice on my much money I should take with me??? which good locations we should check out??? and what hotel or hostel should we stay in???

I&#039;m from U.K btw

Please let me know it full detail...Thank You!!!
</Content>
        <Date>2012-02-20 17:30:35</Date>
        <Timestamp>1329787835</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20120220173034AAj5foC</Link>
        <Category id="396545598">Other - Destinations</Category>
        <UserId>CgbVZUcAaa</UserId>
        <UserNick></UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>1</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>visit the Van Gough museum for sure

don&#039;t bring cash, bring a good credit card 
  

m</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>Zd4aNTI2aa</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>Maverick</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1329793966</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1330307124</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20110805141812AAInm5s" type="Answered">
        <Subject>why is amsterdam allowed to grow weed and other countries cant?</Subject>
        <Content>Cannabis grows in many countries and still it cant be smoked freely anywhere on the planet except amsterdam. Why is that?
</Content>
        <Date>2011-08-05 14:18:12</Date>
        <Timestamp>1312579092</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20110805141812AAInm5s</Link>
        <Category id="396545531">Netherlands</Category>
        <UserId>rUJhvpfNaa</UserId>
        <UserNick></UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>4</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>0</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>Amsterdam is a city not a country and the Netherlands allow legal marijuana use because over all they have a very liberal view on life.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>7at1Hyn8aa</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>Athena</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1312590774</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1313111613</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20110217045226AAvgMAA" type="Answered">
        <Subject>What is the cheapest way to travel from Amsterdam to Brussels and then on to Luxembourg City?</Subject>
        <Content>I&#039;m planning a little adventure. Flying from London to Amsterdam, then somehow travelling from Amsterdam to Brussels. Then from Brussels travelling on to Luxembourg City, and then flying back to London.

Could somebody please tell me the cheapest way to travel from Amsterdam to Luxembourg City via Brussels? If there is a really cheap way that takes a long time any slightly more expensive but quicker alternatives would be welcome too!
Obviously I would prefer it if nobody suggested walking, hitchhiking, stealing a car etc as the cheapest way to get between points!
</Content>
        <Date>2011-02-17 04:52:26</Date>
        <Timestamp>1297947146</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20110217045226AAvgMAA</Link>
        <Category id="396545531">Netherlands</Category>
        <UserId>RlCFojNfaa</UserId>
        <UserNick>lascar</UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>0</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>I agree with the first answer. Cheaper options include taking the Eurolines Coach but it&#039;ll take hours whereas the train from A&#039;dam- Brussels and Brussels-Lux will only take around 2-3 hours.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>AA12105296</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>Kaela</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1298158399</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1298466777</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20080327203920AAeTJ46" type="Answered">
        <Subject>How long does it take to get to Amsterdam from Antwerp by train?</Subject>
        <Content>It looks like I can get a holiday offer(hotel incl.) to Antwerp by Eurostar,but not to Amsterdam. Is it possible to stay in Amsterdam and get to Amsterdam ? Are there good inter-connections by train? (It would be helpful if you could also tell me the name of the train.) Thank you.
</Content>
        <Date>2008-03-27 20:39:20</Date>
        <Timestamp>1206675560</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20080327203920AAeTJ46</Link>
        <Category id="396545565">Other - Destinations</Category>
        <UserId>W9U4Iv5Iaa</UserId>
        <UserNick>hachikopa</UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/sc/28172/answers1/images/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>3</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>Amsterdam and Antwerp are less than about an hour apart by rail, and it isn&#039;t a long drive either.

Amsterdam Centraal and Antwerpen are connected directly, no need to change trains.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>esRI2Dooaa</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>Ed</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1206676903</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1206691408</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20081117162044AAN2wM8" type="Answered">
        <Subject>What parts of Amsterdam are fun to visit?</Subject>
        <Content>Im currently planning a trip to amsterdam and i was wondering if anyone has gone to give me some advise in where to go and what to see. I was also planning on trying to get information on good hotels. 
</Content>
        <Date>2008-11-17 16:20:44</Date>
        <Timestamp>1226967644</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20081117162044AAN2wM8</Link>
        <Category id="396545531">Netherlands</Category>
        <UserId>dyC4tWdzaa</UserId>
        <UserNick>julio g</UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>1</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>A good site with a lot of information is:
http://www.amsterdam.info/

Most of Amsterdam is fun to visit.
Above site has a long list of museums, but also a listing for music, (by clicking on the link you first get a sub page mentioning classical music, but from there you can get modern music too.)

And read the older questions here, as this is a question that comes up about daily, gives you many good ideas from many people.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>zBWefnYHaa</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>Willeke</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1226989618</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1227486927</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20111004095627AArfecM" type="Answered">
        <Subject>When is the Amsterdam Coffee shop ban for tourists going to take place?</Subject>
        <Content>I was planning on going to Amsterdam around november/ december. However I don&#039;t know when the tourist ban will take place. Will it be in this time period?
</Content>
        <Date>2011-10-04 09:56:27</Date>
        <Timestamp>1317747387</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20111004095627AArfecM</Link>
        <Category id="396545531">Netherlands</Category>
        <UserId>4AebFYmfaa</UserId>
        <UserNick></UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>0</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>No. I don&#039;t expect it this year. Way things are going and the distractions our politicians face now I really don&#039;t think we&#039;ll see anything before queens day.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>SfUJhzfAaa</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick></ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1317753605</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1318266825</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20081021192347AA8XUUb" type="Answered">
        <Subject>How much money should I save for Amsterdam?</Subject>
        <Content>So I&#039;m going to Amsterdam for my spring break next year, how much money should I save from now till then? I am planning on smoking and going to a hotel. Also, I want to go to clubs and eat out. Thank you. This is from New York to Amsterdam.
</Content>
        <Date>2008-10-21 19:23:47</Date>
        <Timestamp>1224642227</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20081021192347AA8XUUb</Link>
        <Category id="396545531">Netherlands</Category>
        <UserId>o1fDgPOgaa</UserId>
        <UserNick>Jacks</UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/sc/28172/answers1/images/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>0</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>How long are you staying and are you traveling with a group? 
Make a budget for every day for the plans you have. 
If you&#039;re going for 5 days, i guess you can easily spend €50  a day with your plans. 
The hotel cost will be around €50 a nite (for 1 person based on a double room). You can opt to stay in an hostel, that&#039;s way cheaper and quite proper.. 
So it would add up to about €500 ($625 today&#039;s rate). Excluding your airline fair, I guess that will also cost you about $600. 
Hope you&#039;ll have a nice time, Amsterdam is really fun. If you have time visit Rotterdam as well, also a nice place with lots of things to do and cheaper than A&#039;dam/less touristy. 
p.s. the smoking part, that is a real waste of money. Check some guides for the best places to do that and avoid the Bulldog, that&#039;s a tourist trap. The clubbing is great.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>6D7HvCzAaa</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>Chaan</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1224751887</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1225161836</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
    <Question id="20070922125533AA83KkN" type="Answered">
        <Subject>How far away is Amsterdam Airport Schiphol from the center of the city of Amsterdam?</Subject>
        <Content>I have a four hour layover at Amsterdam airport, do you think it is wise to check out the city of Amsterdam, or just stay and wait in the airport?
</Content>
        <Date>2007-09-22 12:55:33</Date>
        <Timestamp>1190490933</Timestamp>
        <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20070922125533AA83KkN</Link>
        <Category id="396546521">Air Travel</Category>
        <UserId>1tTAnI0Paa</UserId>
        <UserNick>Liz</UserNick>
        <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/sc/28172/answers1/images/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
        <NumAnswers>5</NumAnswers>
        <NumComments>0</NumComments>
        <ChosenAnswer>Depends really where you are flying to.  It doesnt take long to get in the city.  It is just one train ride away and the trains go very very frequently there.  The problem is what does take a long time is the airport security along with checkin (especially if traveling using a regional discount airline)  Most discount airlines close strictly 30-40 minutes before a flight departure.  Then you have to worry about getting through the checkpoints and all of that. 

So you really have 3 hours twenty minutes minus giving an hour for traveling back and forth.  Plus to play it safe I&#039;d give an extra thirty minutes minimum leeway for additional time.  

So your looking at an hour and twenty minutes of actual city time.

You have to decide... personally, I prefer to be early and not have to worry about rushing around places. Plus with the increased security... you can never be so sure how long it takes to get through airport security. But yes, you do have enough time to at least see a little bit of the city.  Enough to say you were there.  The red light district is close to the train station... so you can see that.  If you decide to go just remember to double check the schedule where you buy your tickets to make sure there are no changes.  But trains to and from Schipol leave practically all hours of the day and are very very frequent.</ChosenAnswer>
        <ChosenAnswererId>AA12008040</ChosenAnswererId>
        <ChosenAnswererNick>NotoFroto</ChosenAnswererNick>
        <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1190493663</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
        <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1191119548</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    </Question>
</ResultSet>

